Want to create amazing videos with
你想用什么方式制作精彩的视频？
artificial intelligence even without knowing
人工智能仍未可知
anything about it? Cick is the tool
这些都不是 CCK，只有这个工具。
you
你
need. [Music] Cing is an
你需要cing。它是一种工具
artificial intelligence tool that allows you
人工智能可以让你
to create videos from text or
使用文本创建视频或
images. It was released in mid-
中间有一张图片出现在市场上。
2024 and has had
从2024年起，情况有所改善。
impressive improvements, and I can tell you this because I've been
令人印象深刻，我这么说是因为我亲眼见过。
using it since the initial version.
我从最初版本就开始使用它了。
But it only creates Clean videos. I'm going
但它在那里只能生成清晰的视频。就是这样。
to answer that in this video where
我将在本视频中回答这个问题。
you'll learn all about the tool and, above all, how to
您将了解所有工具和
use it. Hello
最重要的是，你将学会如何使用它。你好
crew, I'm Lwin Enrique, and this is
船员：我是伊温·恩里克，这是
Artificial Ark, a channel dedicated to
人工方舟运河，献给
generative artificial intelligence, especially
生成式人工智能
the generation of videos and images
一切与视频和图像的生成有关
with artificial intelligence. Today I'm going to
有了今天的人工智能，我将……
show you everything related to Clean.
显示所有与清洁相关的内容
I hope it works for you and that you like it. Let's
希望它对你有用，也希望你喜欢它。
begin. And the answer to my
让我们开始吧，我的问题的答案是……
previous question is that Cing doesn't only
前一个是不仅 cing
make videos. That's why I want to show you
他制作视频，所以我才想给你们看。
from scratch how to access the page, how to search for it,
如何从头开始访问该页面
how to get it, so we can then move
如何找到它，如何得到它，然后出发
forward and start creating and learning about
继续前进，开始创造和学习
all its tools. As always, the
他所有的工具一如既往
first thing you'll do is type Cck into
首先，它会在那里输入 cck
Google, click search, and it will appear
我们用谷歌搜索，就会出现结果。
as the first option.  Clicking here takes
在第一个选项中，当你点击时
you directly to the page, and as
我们直接进入了页面，然后……
you'll see, you'll have a menu with everything:
你会看到，你会得到一份包含所有菜品的菜单。
Exploration, Home, Images,
它包含：家居探索图片
Videos, My Creations. Also
我的作品视频以及
in the center of the page, you'll
页面中央的菜单与之前相同。
see many videos created by
让我们来看看。许多视频都创造了这一切
the Clean community, which are
清洁社区，以及他们即将离开
posted here based on likes and
根据点赞数在此处发布内容，根据……
views. It's super cool! The
播放起来非常流畅，而且超级酷
top right clearly shows "
右上角部分会显示你
Sign in for free credits," meaning
clarito 免费登录即可获得积分
connect to get
登录即可获得积分
free credits. Just register, and you're all set. They wo
只需注册即可免费使用。
n't charge you anything. When
好的，完事后他们不会收你任何费用。
you register or create an account, you'll
您注册或创建帐户后，您将
receive
收到
366 coins or credits to
366 个金币或积分，这样你就可以
generate videos in the tool. One of
使用工具一生成视频
the pros is that it's completely free; you do
优点是完全免费
n't have to pay or enter
你无需付费或参与。
credit card information or anything. Just
仅限信用卡或类似物品
creating an account gives you these
创建账户后，您将获得这些权益。
credits. The downside is that
这样做的缺点是……
generation is very slow when you don't have a
那一代人，当你没有……
plan, if you're not on the free one.
如果你用的不是免费套餐，那就得另购套餐了。正是这一点
But let's see what Clean offers. On the
速度很慢，但我们看看传送带能带来什么。
left side, you'll see
在左侧，你会看到它有
the assets; it only lets you create
也就是说，它只允许你创建资产。
images and videos. Let's start with
图片和视频 让我们从……开始
images. When you enter the area...  The
图片 当你进入该区域时
image tool will let you write a prompt
图片可以帮助你编写提示
to generate the image, and
当然是为了生成图像，而且
below it lets you change the aspect ratio, that is,
您可以在下方更改宽高比或
the size of the image. You decide if you
图片尺寸由你决定。
want it to be square, vertical,
你想要一个竖直的正方形吗？
panoramic, a story, whatever you want.
全景，一个故事，你
Just click and it will be
你想要什么，只需点击一下即可。
marked in green; that's the aspect ratio
绿色标记表示宽高比。
that will generate that image. Below, like
这将生成如下图所示
any artificial intelligence
任何人工智能
image generation tool, it will let you
图像生成会让你瞠目结舌
create four images per
默认情况下，每张图片创建四个。
prompt by default. In this case, you can lower it
在这种情况下，你可以下载它。
to one or increase it to nine. I'm
可以增加到一，也可以增加到九，我就是这么做的。
going to leave it at four. I'm putting
我决定就定在四这个数字。我正在放置
a luxury model in the prompt, who is
在舞会上，一位奢侈模特……
in a photo shoot with a
在一次摄影活动中
haute couture dress with many
高级定制礼服，款式多样
details, glamorous, with
那些令它充满魅力的细节，那些……
professional lighting and a little more. I'm
专业的灯光，还有一点我自己的想法。
going to change the aspect ratio to 916 so that it's like
我打算将宽高比改为 916。
a story,
就像一个故事一样。
and I'm going to generate it. We have a
我将生成它，我们有一个
result that doesn't look bad at all. The
结果看起来还不错。
lighting on the face and
脸上的光线
body looks superb. It looks a little
车身看起来很棒，看起来有点……
unreal, but it looks superb; it looks like
难以置信，但看起来棒极了，它看起来像
the photos have already been retouched. I'm going to
我打算……他们已经把照片修好了。
add a much more basic prompt, which is a
Acar un prom mucho más básica que es un
dog with a red hat.
戴着红色帽子的狗
Alice in Wonderland style.
爱丽丝梦游仙境
Why? I want to try this because there are
我想尝试一下，因为有
AI programs that don't let you
不具备这种能力的人工智能
add such direct references
它们允许这种直接引用
as Alice in Wonderland,
就像爱丽丝梦游仙境一样
for example. My Journey allows it, but
例如，我的旅程会离开它，但
Firefly doesn't. I want to show you how
萤火虫，我不想教你怎么做。
Clean works with a
Clean 可以通过示例来解决这个问题。
direct example. It creates four really
Direct 创建了四个超级图像
cool images. I really like all
我非常喜欢它们。
four images. I like this one a lot, this one too.
四张图，我最喜欢这张。
These are kind of serious, but they're
他们看起来很严肃，但他们其实是
really cool. What can you do with a
超级可爱。用它能做什么？
photo? If you have a photo, you can scale it.
你可以通过调整照片的大小来缩放照片。
If you click here, you can scale it and
点击这里即可攀爬
increase the quality. At the top, you can
您可以提高以上质量。
copy it, like it,
你可以复制它，喜欢它，或者不喜欢它……
dislike it, share it, add it to your
喜欢就分享，拥有就归你
favorites, or simply
收藏或您可以简单地
download it. It gives you two options: download with
下载时有两种选择：使用以下方式下载
the watermark or download without the
带水印或不带水印的下载
watermark. Another important detail is that when
另一个重要的事实是，当
you use the free version of Clean, everything you
您可以使用免费的“全部清理”选项。
download will have a
你即将失败的标志是……
watermark. Otherwise, you can simply remove it by paying. Let's continue. At the
水，或者，如果不是，那就现在付钱。
bottom, I've already increased the quality. I can
我已经提高了下面的质量，我可以
use it as a reference, or I can bring it
我可以把它作为参考资料吗？或者我可以把它提出来吗？
to life. How does this work? I repeat, "bring to
赋予生命，这该如何做到，我再说一遍，赋予生命
life." You click, and it will take you to...
人生，你点击它，它就会带你去……
You can make it into a video. The great thing about this
你可以把它拍成视频，这是它的优点。
is that you directly create an image with
就是直接用……创建图像
Clean and bring it into the same application
清洁后，你可以在同一个应用程序中保存它。
to the section where you can create it as a
进入可以创建它的部分
video. This
视频，或者你可以制作这个视频
is super cool. Normally you create an
太酷了，你通常会做一件
image in Journey, Firefly, or
萤火虫之旅中的图像
Leonardo and then bring it into an
莱昂纳多，然后你把她带到一个
application like this. Here, it
也可以直接在这里应用此方法。
's all integrated. Let's see, let's
它是集成式的，嗯，我们来看看……
try it. In this promo, I'm going to put that
我打算把它放到这个推广活动中进行测试。
the dog is barking. Notice that the
注意，狗在叫。
video generation already increases the
视频生成技术已经日益普及
credits. A generation of four
信用评级为四代
credits in an image to a video is 35.
视频图片中包含 35 个演职人员信息。
Let's see what it gives us. While the
让我们看看他能激发我们身上哪些潜能。虽然
video is being generated, it's important to tell you
生成的视频很重要，它可以告诉你
that whenever you're going to generate something, it might not work the
无论何时你要创作什么
first time.
也许第一次你永远不会……
This is normal. Many
外出。这是正常现象。许多
people think that generating an image or a
人们认为生成图像
video works the first time. And this is
视频第一次尝试就成功了。这就是
because all the AIs
测试是因为所有智能
that generate videos or images work
制作视频或图像的人
differently. So you can't work with them
不同的。那你就没法和他们共事了。
all the same way. So if you don't get it right
都一样。所以如果不是
the first time, try again.
你知道第一个，再试一次。
Change the promo, the setup, the
改变了舞会的方式
lighting; you have to keep testing. It's
需要测试一下照明设备。
generated now. Let's see it, and it proves
它是生成的，让我们看看，它证明了我们
this: a barking dog doesn't turn around.  It doesn't even
这是一只吠叫的小狗，它甚至都不回头。
sit, it just stands up straight and barks, it turns around
如果它站不直还会吠叫，那感觉会很糟糕。
like it's been called, but it's not bad. By the way,
她转过身来，就像他们叫我一样，但是
I only put
顺便说一句，这还不错，我只是放了一下。
a Start button. If I had put it here at
如果我把它放在这里，那就算是开始了
the end, the dog would be far away. The image would make
最后，小狗离开了画面。
that transition from the sitting dog to the
从坐姿狗到
far away dog. But let's go back to the
狗走开，但我们还是回到正题吧。
images because there's another function that I really
图片，因为还有另一个功能需要用到。
like and I want to show it to you. We're going
我很喜欢它，想给你看看。
to the second button or the second
我们将转到第二个按钮或第二个按钮。
tool option, which is the Virtual
虚拟工具选项
Try On, which is something new. We have it to
试穿，这是我们新推出的功能。
create a model. Let's create a guy, I
让我们创建一个模型，让我们创建一个男孩
'm setting him to be a
我建议他去当歌手。
K-pop singer posing for the camera at a
卡波普在镜头前摆姿势
concert. Let's leave it at 916, the
演唱会，就到916吧。
ranch, and we're going to generate it. Notice that
牧场，我们将要生产，看看那个
here the generation changes to 20
这里世代已经变为20代了。
credits. It creates a K-pop singer.
演职员表创建了一个变调夹歌手
What options does Clean give you when you create
创建时，Clean 会提供哪些选项？
an image with the Virtual Try On? At the
一张我进行虚拟试穿的图片
bottom, it gives you Outfit, Upscale,
下半部分让你拥有高档的造型
Span, and Bring to Life. The same goes for Ovale; we
跨越并赋予生命，与奥巴莱相同
already know what Bring to Life does. We already
我们已经知道“赋予生命”功能的作用了。
know what Spine does. For now, it's
我们目前只知道脊柱的功能。
free, and what this means is that it's going to
它是免费的，这意味着什么呢？
expand it a little because
这将使其略微膨胀，因为
I want this photo to be... I mean, to
我希望这张照片是……我的意思是，
be  like a thumbnail, and I'm going to
就像个微缩模型，我会把它给它。
expand it. We already have the expanded photo; he
我们已经有了放大后的照片。
's at his concert. But what I
他正在参加他的演唱会，但是……
really wanted to show you about this
我真的很想给你看这个
function is the following: the outfit, or the "i
功能如下：服装或我
outfit." Look at this. If I click on "i
服装观察此如果我按下i
outfit" here, it will take me to this option,
点击“在此处选择服装”会将我引导至此选项。
which is right here. We
就是这里，或者更确切地说，就是这里。
have this option here. What does it mean? I'm
我们还有这个选择。这意味着什么？
going to tell the
我要告诉情报部门
artificial intelligence to put this flannel or
人造的，把这种法兰绒穿上或
this shirt on my photo. I'm using
这件衬衫和我的照片很像。我穿着它。
the default ones that the
默认的那些
artificial intelligence gives you. To see the
人工智能。这样你就能看到
example, I click "generate," and it changes.
例如，我点击生成，它就改变了。
As you can see, the generation isn't very
正如你所看到的，这一代人并不那么……
exact because here it shows a
没错，因为这里向你展示了如何
blur; the hand looks a little strange.
没有模糊效果，手看起来有点奇怪。
However, this is because, obviously, it's
然而，这很显然是因为他就是。
inserting the shirt here, but the hand
把衬衫插在这里，但是手
is where it should be. But it still
它放在了应该在的位置，但内容却完全一样。
places it; that is, it fulfills the objective in
它将其放置在那里，也就是说，它实现了目标。
this instance. To do one last example,
这条提示是为了举最后一个例子。
which is a girl posing for the
这位摆姿势的女孩是谁？
camera with her hands in her pocket, wearing
口袋里的相机
a red jacket and jeans, I'll bring her in.
我穿了一件红色外套和牛仔裤。
I find my model, I select it, and I'm going
我带来了。我在找我的模型，我做好标记就走。
to say, "Let's see if it generates another
我们看看它是否会生成另一个。
jacket," and it's going to tell me to put this one on,
外套，我要告诉自己穿上它
which is like a sweatshirt, and...  I'm going to
这件像运动衫一样的衣服，我要……
generate it when it's created. Okay, the
创建时将其设置为生成。好了，就这些。
first girl is in a red jacket with jeans and
第一夫人身穿红色夹克和牛仔裤
her hands in her pockets. The second girl has her
双手插兜，第二个
hands in her
因为双手插在口袋里
jacket pockets, and the jeans here look a little
外套和牛仔裤露出来了一点。
blurry. But that's part
就像模糊一样。但唉，这也是其中的一部分。
of the process. The same girl is on a
创作和同一个背景女孩
white background. Here I confirm the difference
我确认白色与白色之间的区别
between the person posing
摆姿势的人和模特之间存在一段距离。
with their hands on their face, tucked inside
他们双手捂着脸，在里面
their outfit, and them not getting in the way when
从服装到确保它们不会碍事
creating the images. Secondly,
在创建图像时
the white background will help a lot
白色背景会很有帮助。
to avoid that blurring that
这样就不会有其他模糊之处了。
was in the others. So now we have
其他的也有。所以我们已经有了
two new pieces of information to create these
创建这些数据需要两条新数据。
images. That's why I want to ask you the
所以我才想问问你关于这些图片的事。
following: Did you like what you've
您当时喜欢以下内容
seen in this first part?
你在第一部分中看到的是……
Click there and subscribe. Now
它提供点击订阅的选项。
leave a comment if you have
如有任何意见，请留言。
any questions, want to share
您有什么问题或意见想分享吗？
information, say hello,
信息评论问候
or subscribe. That will help
评论但订阅，那将会
the channel grow and reach more
发展频道，触达更多人
people who, like you, want to learn
像你这样想学习的人
about Artificial Intelligence. Let's get to what we've been waiting for:
关于人工智能，我们开始吧
video creation with Clean.
正如预期的那样，视频制作过程非常顺利。
Now we go back to the initial menu. We're going
现在我们回到最初的菜单。
to click on videos. We have
我们点击视频，我们有……
version 1.6, which is...  New 1.5 and 1.1. In
版本 1.6 是 1.5 和 1.1 版本新增的。
1.1, I want to show you several videos I
1.1 我想给你们看几个视频
created because I was making chairs, and
我创作它的原因是我当时在制作椅子，
this is a video in version
这是该版本的视频
1.0. I created this image in my Journey. I
1.0 我在我的旅程中创作了这幅图像
added a prompt, kept the settings as they
我添加了一个提示符，并保留了原有设置。
were, and the camera movement, which
镜头移动即将开始
wasn't available at the time,
当时还没有这个功能
and the Negative Prompt. What are Negative
负面因素有哪些？
Prompts? This is what you want to be
这是你最不希望看到的。
hidden from the image. Everything you put
图片中所有内容都会显示出来。
in this section won't be generated by the
本部分不会生成它
AI. In version
版本的人工智能
1.1, the credits for generating a video
1.1 视频生成积分
were 10 credits. In this second version, the
第二部电影有10个学分。
katana had one more movement. Why?
这把武士刀还有最后一个动作，为什么？
Because Clean has an option
因为 Clean 有一个选项是
called motion blur, which is the
它被称为运动模糊，即对……的控制
motion control. If you click on draw motions, it
如果你按下绘制动作按钮，你就会移动。
opens another tab. Then you have options to
打开另一个标签页。那么你就必须
write, to delete, of
你必须写明要删除，因为
course. Here, you click here; it's much
当然，这里。嗯，你把它给这里，这可不少。
faster. Here you change the size. Here
这里速度更快，这里更改尺寸
you have options to auto-segment an area, and
您是否可以选择划分区域用于停放车辆？
here you apply certain movements.
在这里，你需要进行一些特定的动作。
In this case, which was the first
在这种情况下，这是第一个
option, I didn't do it. In the second one, it
如果你选择第二种方案，我没有这样做。
tells you to apply four. Let's see.
他说我申请了四份，我们来看看。
Seeing them, fixed area one says the arm should
看到它们修复了区域一，说明手臂
move this way. Area two is the
二号区域向这个方向移动
purple one, which would be this arm and this
紫色部分指的是这条手臂和这部分。
katana. I told it to move this way.
我让卡塔娜挪过来。
Area three is the blue one, that the
第三区域是蓝色的，也就是身体所在的区域。
person's body should move to the right. And
这个人向右移动，然后
area five is the smoke, and I told it to
第五区。是烟味，我就是这么跟他说的。
move in a circular motion, as if there were
它做着圆周运动，仿佛它曾经
movement throughout the smoke. That's why
烟雾中的一切运动
the smoke is coming out here. The
这就是为什么这里会冒烟，烟雾正在移动。
person's body moved
那人的身体向
forward. The katana moved a little,
她面前的武士刀微微动了一下。
but above all, the movement is here.
但最重要的是，这场运动已经到来。
Another example I want to show you is with
我想向你们展示的另一个例子是……
a person. I think the
我认为一个人的困难
biggest difficulties in creating
比那些存在于创造层面的事物更大
images or converting images to videos are with
图片或将图片转换为视频是与
people because of their gestures and
人们通过手势，通过
movements, which are sometimes super fake, and that's not what I
动作有时非常虚假
like, at least. That's why I don't upload many videos
我喜欢它，所以很多视频才不喜欢它。
because I don't like them.
我买它们是因为我其实并不喜欢它们。
But look at this one. So you can see that I created it
但请看看这个，这样你就能看出这是我创作的。
with Clean in version 1.0. I created the girl
在 1.0 版本中用 Clean 给女孩
in M ​​Journey and a prompt, and I made it
我在 Journey 中创建了它，并添加了一个提示……
so that the girl is sitting on
我这样说，就好像女孩正坐在……
the bus and moving around.  It's as
公交车开始行驶，就像……
if she were on the bus, moving
如果她在那儿，公交车就会在那儿。
away from the initial location. In this case, I did
在这种情况下，要远离最初的地点。
n't do any drawing motion; I
我没有做任何绘画动作，但是
simply let her
我只是让她自己决定什么时候处理。
do it as she saw fit.
他尽其所能地去理解它。
Similarly, I used the same girl,
我对这个女孩也做了同样的事。
told her to be walking, and she created it. It's
我让他走，他就做到了。
not bad, but I don't completely like it either.
不算差，但我也不喜欢。
But in this case, we're going to create
一切，但在这个例子中，我们将要创造
some new things and try
新事物，我们将尝试一下
version 1.6. The first thing I'm going to try
我首先要尝试的是1.6版本。
is the test to video. I'm going to write a
这是视频测试，我要写一篇
promo of a sports car speeding
舞会，那是一辆跑车步行
through a city, and I want the
全速穿过城市，然后
video to be quite
视频风格相当……
commercial-style. I'm going to set the settings to be
商业环境会表明这一点。
quite creative.
这个模型需要相当有创意。
We set the model to professional, which
我们已经把这件事专业化了，这正是他想要的。
means it takes a little longer, and the
我的意思是，这需要更长的时间，而且
quality is much better than in
质量比……好得多
standby mode. I want it to generate a
我希望它能为我生成一个站立模式。
single video; I'm not going to write any
只有视频，我不打算写任何东西。
negative promo, and we're going to click generate.
负平均值，我们将要制造它。
As you can see, even with a
正如你所看到的，即使制定计划也是必要的。
paid plan, the video is generated in 9 minutes.
9分钟内即可完成支付。
Imagine how long it can take with the
想象一下这需要多长时间……
free plan! That's why I say it's
这就是免费方案的内容。这就是我为什么说
one of the drawbacks; however, it
然而，这也是缺点之一。
works.  To try it out, to use it and
有用。试用一下，用一下。
get the most out of it, if you don't mind
如果你不介意的话，就好好利用一下吧。
waiting, this is the option: a
等待也是一种选择，一代人的时间。
simple generation, a car driving in the
简单来说，就是一辆车在路上行驶。
city with traffic, and this fulfills the
交通繁忙的城市，这满足了
objectives. I think we did ask for it to be
我认为我们当时要求的是目标。
something commercial. Well, not so much,
是商业性质的吗？其实不然。
but it fulfills the objective: the car driving through
但为了实现目标，汽车正在行驶
life at full speed. Well, there you have it,
以全速生活？好了，就这些。
a modern sports car. Now let's get
现代跑车现在
to an important point. I'm sure
我们来谈谈一个非常重要的方面。
you have this question: Is there any parameter
你可能会问：是否存在参数？
or way to write the promo, both
或者用某种方式来写舞会
for text and for images, and take it to
无论是文本还是图像，并将其带到
video? Yes, there is, and it's the following: in the
是的，有一段视频，就是下面这段。
case of a photo, to write the
照片案例是这样写的
promo you have to write a subject, a
舞会上你必须写一个主题
person, an animal, whatever you want to
人、动物，任何你想要的
appear in this image, and describe it: a
它出现在这张图片中，请你描述一下它。
golden retriever dog painted blue.
涂成蓝色的金毛寻回犬
This is your subject. Then you have to
如果你的主题是这个，那么你必须……
add movement to the subject: the
为主题增添动感
golden retriever dog painted blue
涂成蓝色的金毛寻回犬
walks forward. Then comes a
向前走，然后出现了
scene; you have to describe the scene: it
场景，你需要描述场景。
's in a green forest with grass and
它位于一片绿草茵茵的森林中。
colorful trees. Then you can add
然后你可以添加色彩缤纷的树木
a very defined camera style. For
一种非常鲜明的摄影风格
example, I want it to be a Sony such and such, a
例如，我希望它是索尼某某型号。
Nikon such and such. You can add that it's
尼康相机，你可以补充说它是
4K, 8K, you can add a type of
4K 8K 你可以添加一种类型
lighting. Look, I  I want it to have
灯光方面，我希望它是……
cinematic lighting. So you
电影级照明
can add this after you
您可以在之后添加此内容
've added the subject, its
您已添加了您的主题是什么。
movement, and the scene. In the case of
场景和运动情况
when you already have an image and want to turn it into a
当你已经有了图片并且想要保留它的时候
video, the structure is as follows:
视频结构如下
the first thing you have to write is the
你首先要写的是
subject, a girl; then you write the
我抱着一个女孩，然后你给她写信。
movement, a girl walking
一个女孩正朝这边走去
forward, a girl walking from left
前方有个女孩向左走。
to right; then you add the background.
然后，在右侧添加背景。
What's happening in the background?
到底发生了什么？
The background recedes, the background moves;
背景逐渐远去
things move. You
挪动东西，所有这些移动
have to explain all this movement in the promo,
你得在舞会上跟他解释清楚。
something very summarized but well explained.
非常简短但解释得很清楚
In the case that you want to extend the
如果你想扩展
image or video you've created, what
你创作的图片或视频是什么？
you have to do is add a subject—it
你需要做的就是添加一个主题
can be the same one—plus the movement
它可以相同，再加上运动。
so that it continues to lengthen the scene. And
这样他就可以继续延长这场戏，
to give an example, I'm going to explain it
举个例子，我来解释一下。
with this promo. For this example, I'm
有了这个提示，我就可以举例说明。
using a photo by MC Journey that I think
我用自己创作的 MC Journey 图片
is a girl on the beach with her
一个女孩和她一起在海滩上
headphones and all that. The promo I
耳机之类的东西。那个色情片
'm giving it is that the girl is
我把它给她。这个女孩是……
walking forward, looking at the
向前走，看着
camera, and that in the background,
相机拍摄的画面，背景模糊不清。
the people are blurred, and they are seen moving normally
人们正常地四处走动。
in this version.  In version 1.6,
1.6 版本中不提供此功能。
the motion brush and
动态画笔还在，但又好像不在了。
camera movement are not yet available.
相机运动中可用
Therefore, the only thing
因此，唯一的事情是
available in this case is the prompt.
在这种情况下，可用的是毕业舞会
When it generates the result, we have
当它生成结果时，我们有
the following: Compared to what I
以下内容与您所做的相比
showed you of the girl at the beginning, which I
我一开始就给那个女孩看了
did with version 1.0, the difference is
我用的是 1.0 版本，区别在于……
huge. I mean, the difference is enormous.
野蛮。我的意思是，差别太大了。
In this one, the girl looks at the camera, walks, her
在这张照片里，女孩看着镜头，然后走了过去。
hair moves naturally, and when she
头发自然摆动
smiles, it's perfect. I mean,
微笑，那就完美了，我是说真的。
the gestures she currently has
这是他目前所展现的姿态。
are perfect. But Clan has another
Clean 很完美，但 Clan 还有另一个版本。
option, which is also something new:
这也是一种全新的选择，即
lip sync.
唇音同步，或唇部同步
Let's try it. For the lip sync,
我们来试试涂在嘴唇上。
we have this button here. We
这里有个按钮，我们按下它
click it, and it will let us either use
点击即可让我们或使用
presets or upload one. In
默认设置，或者我们可以上传一个。
this case, I'm going to upload one when
在这种情况下，我打算上传一个。
I have the audio ready, which is 10
我已经准备好音频了，就是第10段。
seconds. Note that lip sync costs 10
秒。请注意，唇形同步需要花费 10 美元。
credits. I'm going to create it. The
我要注明创作者的姓名。
lip sync generation depends on the
Lipsing 生成取决于
number of seconds; it takes between 10 and
耗时大约为10秒。
12 minutes. When we have it—in
12分钟后我们就把它放进去了
this case, I have it here—I can say
我这里有个例子，我可以这么说。
that it still needs a lot of work.  Let's
还有很多工作要做，我们走吧。
[Music]
[音乐]
see it,
看看它的身体
athlete's body, what moves is nothing else, this is
运动员，所展现的不过如此。
not the same as when he smiled, in
这和我以前微笑的时候不一样，就像在……
this case, his features, look how
在这种情况下，请观察它的特征。
supernatural it is, whereas in this part it's like, I do
另一方面，《邪恶力量》这一部分是
n't know, he still needs
我还不清楚，目前还缺少相关信息。
a lot of work in this aspect. And
这方面需要做大量工作。而且因为
lastly, I want to show you why Clan
最后，我想向你们展示“为什么”家族
is one of the best apps
这是最好的应用程序之一。
currently for making videos, and it's because of
目前主要制作视频，原因是
its interpretation of gestures, and truly, to this day,
他对姿态和真理的解读
it's the best I
时至今日，它仍然是最好的。
've seen in terms of gestures. I want you to
我已经看到了我想要的那种姿态。
see this: I created a photo in M ​​Journey
我在我的旅程中创建了这张照片，所以你可以看到它
of a girl looking scared, and I put
我把一个看起来很害怕的女孩放在了她身上。
a Pro on her, the woman with a terrified face,
一位专业人士，那位面露惊恐的女士，
wanting to cry, and the camera follows the
想哭的冲动，镜头也随之而来。
shot there as if it were a film,
把它当作电影拍摄现场一样对待。
like a movie, and by the way, the
这就像一部电影，顺便说一句，
lighting is cinematic, and it gives me
灯光很有电影感，让我感觉……
this result. Furthermore, let's go back
这个结果更像是，我们还是把它退回去吧。
and I'm going to zoom in on the
我要去
face, the lighting,
放大脸部，脸部，灯光
how it changes, super amazing. And I
它不断变化的方式令人惊叹。
also wanted to do another test with the
我还想用它做另一次测试。
same thing, with the same theme, and here it is.
主题相同，这里也是如此。
Look at the eyes, the face,
看看她，看看她的眼睛，她的脸。
like, what's happening? The lighting
灯光是怎么回事？
here, the
从这里开始
light, how it does here when he breathes, brutal.  It
就像这里一样，当它粗暴地呼吸时，光线就会变得很亮。
seems that the details, the
我想这就是全部细节了。
level of realism that Clean achieves when
细节写实，干净利落。
generating these types of videos,
是时候制作这类视频了
like the one with the girl walking, are
就像那个走路的女孩一样
brutal. There's a
残酷的himo，这其中有很大的区别
huge difference, and it's noticeable. Let's be clear:
很大，这一点显而易见，我们必须明确这一点。
the world of AI-powered video generation
在视频生成领域
is advancing. I
人工智能正在进步。
know that many say, "Ah,
我知道很多人会说“啊，
realism is terrible. There's no good
现实主义很糟糕，根本没有好的现实主义作品。
consistency in a video, especially when creating
在制作视频时保持视频的一致性
characters. There's no
这里没有任何人物，尤其是一个也没有。
consistency; it's not very realistic." And this
一致性并非那么真实存在，而且这一点
is true; there isn't very good consistency,
确实，这方面缺乏很好的一致性。
and the gestures are very strange when
他们的手势非常奇怪
creating, or rather, when creating
创建或创建时间。或者更确切地说，
videos from images. But
通过图像播放视频，但
currently, with Runway and Luma, they have
目前有跑道和luma
improved, and this is improving every
有所改进，而且这正在改善所有方面。
day. The truth is that there is still a
日子还很长，但事实是，时间依然充裕。
lot of work to be done, but this isn't
工作量很大，但这并不是
something that will happen in a year or two.
这个问题一两年后就会出现。
This will be seen in a matter of very
这件事发生在短短几个月内，也可能发生在几年前。
short months, and improvements are seen
几个月后就会看到结果，而且已经看到了。
with each update that
每次更新都有改进
these tools release. And now I
拿出这些工具，现在你
ask you, did you like this video? Did it
我想问问你是否喜欢这个视频。
help you in any way? Leave your comment, and
有帮助吗？请留下您的评论。
of course, subscribe,
当然，记得订阅！订阅关于
especially so that it reaches more people and so that you
这一切都是为了让更多人看到它
are aware of everything.  What's being
你清楚所有正在发生的事情。
created on the channel with and about
在频道中创建关于
Artificial Intelligence, and I hope to see you
人工智能，我希望见到你
in a future video. Before you go, I
在你离开之前，请观看即将发布的视频
want to recommend this video because I
我想推荐这个视频，因为
know you'll be interested. Remember
我知道你会感兴趣的，记住这一点。
that you can also
还有你在这里列出的那些
subscribe up here for easier and
订阅更便捷
simpler access. I hope you'll be a new
简单的。我希望你是一位新人
crew member, and I'll see you in the next
船员们，下次见！
video. Goodbye!
视频告别